[Music]
here's the premise
if you don't want one of these two uh
fellas to be president then you are
crazy do you feel crazy
yeah so do we when did it become
dangerous to have
common sense and how do we escape this
duopoly trap
well we can reject this lunacy together
unity 2020 is a patriotic plan to
restore the republic and empower our
democracy
by nominating two patriots from the left
and the right we can
end the partisan corruption that's
divided us and unite america
is it guaranteed to work no is it
radical
apparently is it crazy yeah but it's the
right kind of crazy
if this stupid year has taught us
anything it's that we have no idea what
is possible
now take one more look at the sensible
candidates
which of these is the future of our
country
unity 2020 common sense is the new crazy